Speaker 1: that I genuinely feel like when you break up with someone and you have a crazy ex, that was how it felt like being fired from a Daily Wire. Daily Wire. Daily Wire. The Daily Wire. The Daily Wire. From a Daily Wire. The Daily Wire. The Daily Wire. Andrew Klavan. Andrew Klavan. My crazy ex-boyfriend, Andrew Klavan. The Daily Wire. Is that the Daily Wire? He does
Speaker 2: some stuff. The Daily Wire. The Daily Wire. The Daily Wire. The Daily Wire. At the
Speaker 1: Daily Wire. The Daily Wire. The Daily Wire. From a Daily Wire. The Daily Wire. The Daily Wire. From a Daily Wire. Take the Daily Wire. The Daily Wire. Ben Shapiro. Ben Shapiro. Dave Smith,
Speaker 1: answer to this question
Speaker 3: might get you kicked off the daily wire. I had to laugh at that. That's really funny. The daily wire. I'm a daily wire. My psycho
Speaker 4: ex-boyfriend. Daily wire. Daily wire. Daily wire. Reagan Conrad. Jeremy Boring. The daily wire. Daily wire. Daily wire. Daily wire. The daily wire. And the daily wire. Daily
Speaker 1: wire. Brett Cooper out at the daily wire. Daily wire. The daily wire. The daily wire. The daily wire. The daily wire. Daily wire. Sign up for the daily wire. I got fired from the daily wire. We're like, she's done. She's toast. The daily wire. The daily wire. Daily wire.
Speaker 5: Ben Shapiro. Fuck you. And the midget horse that you rode in on. And I
was
Speaker 6: like, why are you so obsessed with me?